翻譯:お兄様
時軸:晚風
校對:ELF
校對&壓制:雪夜
本字幕由夜桜字幕組制作
黑蝴蝶
with the on kasumi our grasp, we can finally complete the last part of the puzzle.
現在霞她們在我們手上了,終于可以完成霸業了
and yet, i sense conflict within you
可是,你好像有點猶豫
remember your birthright
別忘了你的使命
damei
不要
damei,ii—ya
不要 不要
iku *2 mataiku
去了, 又要去了
she may have been your sister once, but your are no longer that weak, mortal vessel
她以前是你的姐妹,可你現在不是從前的你了——那樣弱小,凡人之身
go now and fulfill your destiny
去吧 去完成你的使命吧
那個地方有點....
插進來了
i‘m glad you gentlemen understand the situation
很高興先生們能看清現實
rest assured, the lords of hell will reward you handsomely for your...humhummm
我向你們保證,地獄的大人們會大大地獎賞你們
change of heart
為你們的回心轉意
my leage, apologies
主人,對不起打擾了
perfect timing, we were just concluding the negotiations with our new allies
來得正好,我們正在和新盟友商討呢
sir ,i was told to inform you that Hajimorn resists us still, the blood that flows within her veins makes her resistant to corruption
主上,我是來告知您還是不合作,她血管里流動的血讓她不和我們同流合污
oh,you shall see about that
哦,等著瞧吧
i’ll handle this personally, in the meantime, show the gentlemen out
我會親自處理的,現在,送這些先生們出去吧
all blood courses to your veins? but it will save from what is to come
高貴的血讓你忠貞不屈？可它在接下來的“游戲”里可救不了你
but i will not be the one to defy your justety
但我不會來評價你的忠貞
that honor belongs to—dear old daddy
這份殊榮屬于——親愛的爸爸
don't worry, i am certain he will be gentle, after all, he loves you much.
別擔心,我肯定他會很溫柔的,畢竟他以前那么愛你
這什么鬼...不要...
快點住手...求您了
別給我亂動奇怪的地方啊...等..別..
怎么這樣···
在這種地方······,疼.
how does it feel to have your ow father ruining you, do you feel anger
被親爸爸玩是什么感覺,你感覺憤怒嗎
什么鬼啊,這什么鬼啊
拔出來
pennies···ojj
救命啊
emm 亞美蝶
拔出來啊,你夠了啊
里面不行
大大要在我的里面...在我的里面...
quite a fighter
是個狼人
you've lasted longer than the others at least, let that be your one consolation tonight
你比其他人堅持的久一些,至少.就讓那做你今晚唯一的安慰吧
take her away
把她帶下去
sir,Mistress, bother me interruption
主上,夫人,對不起打擾了
speak fool
說吧,傻b
she has escaped, the jailer has found that this morning.
她 已經跑了,獄卒今早發現的
this better a infantile humor,you worm
這最好是個玩笑,你這臭蟲
send a tormentor after her now
派人去抓她,現在,馬上
i believe this is a job for our beloved XXOO
我覺得這是給我們可愛的XXOO準備的任務（大概是自相殘殺之手段
and her new favorite pet
以及她的新寵物
she will hunt her with help of Slightmare——the speed of nightmare
她在slightmare的幫助下會以噩夢般的速度抓住她的
his keen senses will find her in no time
它敏銳的嗅覺會馬上找到她的
聽不懂講道理 馬說話你能聽懂？
the shrine maid will subject her and after she dies
護法會把她抓到,然后她死了以后
we will have some real fun
我們就能爽了
這啥呀！！！
放開··
好像我想跟這些怪物OX一樣
不要啊 快救救我....
求你們了
騙人吧 什么這是,這樣的
啊我已經···
不好,一點都不好,和怪物們,一點都不爽*2
動呀（想要？怎么會想要呢,那里都不是插的地方
高~~高潮了~~~~~
apologies for the wake up call, but i have somebody here who is very excited to see you again
不好意思把你吵醒了,但我這有位十分想和你重逢的“人”
馬哥,he has unfinished business with you
他還有事沒辦完
swallow to get on with it
舔它和它搞好關系哦
那種事情我...
沒有感覺 沒有感覺 沒有感覺 我是不可能因為這樣就有感覺的
不要啊 不行..要高潮了...快繼續抽插我吧....
滾開呀..等等
要壞了···
滾開··畜生
求你了 快拔出去吧
這啥啊
怪物的蛋蛋
要死了 它的大雞巴攪得我要....
要死了
the hour draws near
是時候了
indeed ,i can feel the arch demon's power rising
沒錯 我能感受到大魔王的力量在上升
but fast, we must break the easiest one
但是轉瞬即逝,我們必須從最簡單的入手
my dear queen of blood, you are so eager to corrupt another pet,
哦 我親愛的血之女王,你這么著急要玩壞一個新寵嘛
the fast two were delicious, but this one, this one brims with power.
前面快（很快投降的）的兩位很不錯,但這個,這個可是充滿了能量
she will be a greatest servant yet
她將是個最好的仆人
you say that now, but i sense more of them out there, beyond tokyo, the city where human disappear
你現在承認了？但我感覺到了更多的RBQ,在東京,這座已經沒有人類的城市之外
i sense them too, nothing will save them now.
我也感受到她們的氣息了,現在誰也救不了她們了
the feems will com for them all
小妖們會全世界找她們
shall we head down, we wouldn't want to miss the party
我們該走了,可不能錯過聚會
啊..好狡猾
高潮了~~~
高潮了~高潮了~
好爽啊~我也要高潮了~~~高潮了~~~
真開心那
好爽啊
在我的里面....
好舒服~好舒服啊~
好舒服啊~
高~高潮了~~~~
好厲害啊
好激烈啊
很可愛哦
and now, witness the dawn of a new age of terror, as the sisters of blood go forth, to corrupt and blacken the sky of this world forever.
好的,見證一個新黑暗時代的來臨,血盟姐妹們進化,然后破壞,給這個世界帶來無盡的黑暗
給看了劇情的
這集講的就是紫毛被抓,很能抵抗..充滿了能量,但.
最后孵出來的就是那個紫毛,“重生”加入反派的紫毛,蝴蝶造型,也就是標題 黑蝴蝶
估計在場的其他三位也是先后被抓然后····紫毛是第四個